Inventory of the Konstantin Fotic Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed matter, 1934-1968 (Box 52-60)
  - Daily newspapers, bulletins, and articles, 1934-1968
    - "Yugoslav Emergency Relief Assistance Act of 1950," United States Government printing office (Folder 58: 3)
    - Yugoslav Information Sheet, No. 1, No.2, No.4, No.7, 1946 (Folder 58: 4)
    - Yugoslav News-Bulletin, Vol. I, No.11, July 1942 (Folder 58: 5)
    - Yugoslavia To-Day, printed by John Bellows Ltd, Gloucester, United Kingdom, 1945 (Folder 58: 6)
    - The Yugoslav Review, June 1947 (Folder 58: 7)
    - "Yugoslavia-the Victim," Yugoslav National Committee, London, 1946 (Folder 58: 8)
    - Zajednicar, October 1942 (Folder 58: 9)
    - Zbor, 1935 (Folder 58: 10)
  - Chronological clippings and news press releases, 1944-1963
    - 1944-1946 (Folder 58: 11-18)
    - 1947-1952 (Folder 58: 19-25)
    - 1947-1952 (contd.) (Folder 59: 1-6)
    - 1952-1955 (Folder 59: 7-14)
    - 1952-1955 (contd.) (Folder 60: 1-3)
    - 1956-1957 (Folder 60: 4-9)
    - 1965 (Folder 60: 10)
  - Clippings and news press releases by subject, 1939-1952
    - Josip Broz Tito, 1939-1952
      - General, 1948-1952 (Folder 60: 11-16)
      - "Interview with Marshal Tito," United Nations World, August 1952 (Folder 60: 17)
      - President Franklin D. Roosevelt to Adolf Hitler, 1939 (Folder 60: 18)
      - United Nation conference, 1945 (Folder 60: 19)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 60: 20)
- Photographs, 1927, 1938 and undated. (Box 61)
  Contains black and white prints. Arranged by subject. See also box 63
  - Exhibition on Yugoslavia, circa 1938 (Folder 61: 1-2)
  - Family members, 1927 (Folder 61: 3-4)
- Oversize materials, 1941-1954 and undated (Box 62-64)
  Contains office documents, prints, albums of photographs, maps, and a calendar. Arranged by form
  - Delovodni Protokol strogo poverljive arhive za, office register of documents, 1941-1944 (Folder 62: 1)
  - Delovodni Protokol, office register of incoming documents, March-September 1943 (Folder 62: 2)
  - Photographs, 1954 and undated
    - King Petar with groups of unidentified men, undated (Folder 63: 1)
    - King Petar's visit to Masryk-twon, album of photographs, 1954 (Folder 63: 2)
    - National Congress of the Serbian National Defense Council of America, June 1954 (Folder 64: 1)
  - Yugoslav (Serbo-Croatian) translation of the Four Freedoms, by Rastko Petrovic, circa 1943 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Maps of Yugoslavia at war, drawn by Serge Krizman, 1943 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Srpski Pravoslavni kalendar za, 1946 (Folder 64: 4)
  - Telegrams, photographic copies, 1943-1946 (Folder 64: 5-6)